{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"78/39",
			"answer":"78/39",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"110/11",
			"answer":"110/11",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"630/70",
			"answer":"630/70",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"576/72",
			"answer":"576/72",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"220/44",
			"answer":"220/44",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"672/21",
			"answer":"672/21",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"64/32",
			"answer":"64/32",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"533/41",
			"answer":"533/41",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"882/98",
			"answer":"882/98",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"792/96",
			"answer":"792/96",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"22.1/1.7",
			"answer":"22.1/1.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"246/0.41",
			"answer":"246/0.41",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.16/7.9",
			"answer":"3.16/7.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"61.2/68",
			"answer":"61.2/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.92/7.2",
			"answer":"7.92/7.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.86/9.3",
			"answer":"1.86/9.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.139/10",
			"answer":"0.139/10",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.18/0.74",
			"answer":"5.18/0.74",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"39.9/19",
			"answer":"39.9/19",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.09/8.7",
			"answer":"6.09/8.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}